A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Communications, SG 3, Series 8 FA1465
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Communications, SG 3, Series 8
1928-2009
2000-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA1465
19.93 Cubic Feet 49 letter-size document boxes, 1 standard record storage box.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Commonwealth Fund records were donated to RAC in 1985. The initial transfer of archival records to RAC began in 1986, and transfers continue on a regular basis. This series was donated to RAC in multiple accessions from 2002 through 2009.
Scope and Contents
Material in this Communications series includes: Press Clippings 2000-2002, Commonwealth Fund Publications 2001-2008, and a variety of historical files documenting the history of the Fund, its programs, and it's headquarters - the Harkness House. This series also contains a print archive of the Commonwealth Fund website 2003-2009, including monthly snapshots of the website. Available records also document the Fund's 75th Anniversary celebration and related publications.
- Press Clippings, 2000 January-May (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
- Press Clippings, 2000 June-September (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
- Press Clippings, 2000 October-December (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
- Press Clippings, 2001 January-May (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
- Press Clippings, 2001 June-September (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
- Press Clippings, 2001 October-2002 January (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
- Press Clippings, 2002 February-April (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
- Press Clippings, 2002 April-June (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2001 - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2001 - Annual Report 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Commonwealth Fund Quarterly, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2001, 2001 January-March (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2001, 2001 April-December (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
- Media Coverage of Commonwealth Fund Programs 2001, 2001 January-December (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Program on Medicare's Future (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Improving the Quality of Health Care Services (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Health Care in New York City (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
- Commonwealth Fund Quarterly, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Health Affairs - Web Exclusives, 2003 January-June (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Annual Report 2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - IHP (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Child Development and Preventive Care (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Minority Health Policy (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 - Academic Health Centers (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Newsletters, 1928-1933 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Commonwealth Fund Historical Sketch, 1918-1962 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Edward Stephen Harkness 1874-1918 Biography, 2nd Printing, 1953 October (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Partial Listing of Books Published by the Commonwealth Fund, 1918-1990s (Box 16, Folder 2)
- A Thirty-Six Year Perspective - 1923-1959 - Lester Evans (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund Photos (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2004, 2004 January-April (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
- Historical Photos in the Commonwealth Fund 75th Anniversary Publication - For the Common Good: The Commonwealth Fund 1918-1993 (Binder) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Harkness Family Geneology, from Stephen Clarke, Esg. Developed by H.B. Warden, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund Chronological Photo Album 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2004, 2004 May-August (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2003 and 2004, 2003 September, 2004 September (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2004, 2004 October-December (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2005 - Annual Report 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2005, 2005 January-May (Box 19, Folder 4-6)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2005, 2005 May-December (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2006, 2006 January-May (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2006, 2006 June-December (Box 22, Folder 1-6)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2007, 2007 January-May (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2007, 2007 June-December (Box 24, Folder 1-6)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2007 - Annual Report 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2008 - Annual Report 2007 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2008, 2008 January-May (Box 25, Folder 3-7)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2008, 2008 June-December (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Health Grants in New York City, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Minority Health History, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Arthur Ashe, 1992 July (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Community Health, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Child Guidance Clinic, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Communications Plan 1998 and Planning Documents, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund History (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Greenwood Encyclodedia - Commonwealth Fund Sketch, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Harkness Photos, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Harkness House - History of the Fifth Avenue Mansion (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Awards, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Commonwealth Fund: A Thirty-Six Year Perspective - 1923-1959 - Lester J. Evans (Box 27, Folder 7)
- 75th Anniversary Historical Booklet - For the Common Good: The Commonwealth Fund, 1918-1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Harkness - Contribution to the Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Phillips Exeter Academy - Exhibit December 1994, 1994 December (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Commonwealth Fund Fellows 1938-1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- 75th Anniversary Celebration - Budget and Events, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Arhtur Ashe - HIV Positive Announcement, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Report on the Program Department - Staffing and Management, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Harkness House Literature Search and History, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Newsletters, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Commonwealth Fund History - Child Development, 1993-2000 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Harkness Fellowships - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- History of the Fund (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Sam Bloom - Lester Evans Interview (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund History, 1990s (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Books Published by Commonwealth Fund up to 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- History of New York City Grantmaking (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Improving Public Spaces and Services Program - Board Presentation, 2009 November (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Historical Excerpts (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Commonwealth Fund - Program Pamphlets, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Improving Public Spaces and Services Program - Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- World Health Organization - 50th Anniversary Symposium - Safe Motherhood for All, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Annual Report 1988 - Photos (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 30, Folder 4)
- New York Academy of Medicine - Margaret E. Mahoney Symposium on the State of the Nation's Health, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Karen Davis - Photographs (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Commonwealth Fund Newsroom (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Commonwealth Fund Washington Health Policy Week in Review, 2003 December-2004 November (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Home Page, 2004 November 8 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Grantee Spotlights, 2004 November 8 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Data and Surveys, 2004 November 5 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Clinical Tools and Quality Improvement Innovations, 2004 November 5 (Box 31, Folder 7-8)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Foundation History, 2004 November 5 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - President's Column, 2004 August; October 2004 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Programs and Grants (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Quality Matters: Commonwealth Fund Quality Colloquium Newslettter, 2004 September-October (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Email Alerts, 2003 April-2004 November (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2005 January-May (Box 32, Folder 2-6)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2005 May-June (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2005 August-November (Box 33, Folder 3-6)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2005 December-2006 April (Box 34, Folder 1-6)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2006 May-September 2006 (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2006 October-December (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2007 January-April (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2007 April-June (Box 38, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2007 July-November (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2007 December-2008 April (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2008 May-August (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
- Commonwealth Fund Website - Monthly Web Snapshots, 2008 September-2009 January (Box 42, Folder 1-5)
- Book Program - The Land That Feeds Us, Hart, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Book Program - The Transforming Principle, McCarty, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- The City Journal, 1992 Spring (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Physicians, Law and Ethics, Chapman, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2009 - 1-70 (with Index) (Box 44, Folder 1-7)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2009 - 71-140 (with Index) (Box 45, Folder 1-7)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2009 - 141-144 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Commonwealth Fund 2009 - Blog Posts (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2010 - 1365-1424 (with Index) (Box 46, Folder 3-7)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2010 - 1425-1465 (with Index) (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
- Commonwealth Fund 2010 - Blog Posts (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund Publications 2010 - Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Reports - Miscellaneous, 1978-1991 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund Commission on Elderly People Living Alone - Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
- Reports and Surveys, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
- Reports and Surveys, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
- Reports and Surveys, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2-4)